photosofthedays.com 2018-03-29

# Privacy

This Privacy Policy was last updated on June 14, 2013.

Welcome to App Discovery Engine, Inc. (“App Discovery Engine”, “we”, “us” and/or “our”). This privacy policy has been created to provide information about our company and its gaming and messaging applications and related services (together with the Sites, the “Services”) to our users (“you”, “your”). This Privacy Policy sets forth App Discovery Engine’s policy with respect to information including personally identifiable data (“Personal Data”) and other information that is collected from users of the Services and visitors to the websites owned or operated by App Discovery Engine (the “Sites”). 

Information We Collect:

When you interact with us through the Services, we may collect Personal Data and other information from you, as further described below:   
Personal Data That You Provide Through the Services: We collect Personal Data (for example, name and email address) from you when you voluntarily provide such information such as when you register for or enable access to the Services, use certain Services, contact us with inquiries or respond to one of our surveys. Wherever App Discovery Engine collects Personal Data we make an effort to provide a link to this Privacy Policy. By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of App Discovery Engine and the authorized third parties referred to herein located in the United States.   
Non-Identifiable or Aggregated Data: When you interact with App Discovery Engine through the Services, we receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information. Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. App Discovery Engine may store such information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by App Discovery Engine affiliates, agents or service providers. The Services may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the information about the number of messages you send and receive, the total number of visitors to our Services, the number of visitors to each page of our Sites, the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers, and how our users use and interact with the Service. Also, in an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Services, App Discovery Engine often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis. Except to the extent prohibited by the developer terms of any Third Party Services (defined below) to which we have agreed (if any), App Discovery Engine may share this non-identifiable and aggregate data with its affiliates, agents and business partners, but this type of non-identifiable and aggregate information does not identify you personally; in addition, App Discovery Engine may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes. 

Cookies: In operating the Services, we may also use a technology called "cookies." A cookie is a piece of information that the computer that hosts our Services gives to your browser when you access the Services. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the Services and help us analyze Services usage more accurately. For instance, our Services may set a cookie on your browser that allows you to access the Services without needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the Services. In all cases in which we use cookies, we will not collect Personal Data except with your permission.   
However, we or a data provider we have engaged may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads or content. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, that we may share with any third party, solely in hashed, non-human readable form.   
On most web browsers, you will find a “help” section on the toolbar. Please refer to this section for information on how to receive notification when you are receiving a new cookie and how to turn cookies off. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on because they allow you to take advantage of some of the Services features. 

Our Use of Your Personal Data and Other Information:   
App Discovery Engine uses the Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by email, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide Personal Data in order to obtain access to features of the Services, we will use your Personal Data to provide you with access to such services and to monitor your use of such services. App Discovery Engine and its subsidiaries and affiliates (the “Related Companies”) may also use your Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information collected through the Services to help us customize the Services or the messages you receive, improve the content and functionality of the Services, to better understand our users and to improve the Services. App Discovery Engine and its Related Companies may use this information to communicate with you regarding the Services or to tell you about offers, deals and advertisements for the products or services of our partners that we believe will be of interest to you. In addition, we may also share your Personal Data with third party partners that we trust, so that they may contact you with information or offers that they believe may be of interest to you. Any marketing communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to "opt-out" of receiving future marketing communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future marketing communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below. Note however that as user of the Service you cannot opt-out of some administrative communications that are reasonably necessary to the Service, such as billing or service notifications.   
If App Discovery Engine intends on using any Personal Data in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which the Personal Data is collected. 

Our Disclosure of Your Personal Data and Other Information:   
We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:   
Business Transfers: As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets. Related Companies: We may also share your Personal Data with our Related Companies for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.   
Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties: App Discovery Engine, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include sending email, mailing information, maintaining databases and processing payments. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function. L  
egal Requirements: App Discovery Engine may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of App Discovery Engine, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Services or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability. 

Your Choices:   
You can access the Sites without providing any Personal Data. If you choose not to provide any Personal Data, you may not be able to use certain parts of the Services. You may request that we delete your account, and any information associated with your account, but please note that we may be required (by law or otherwise) to retain this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements). When we delete your information, it will be deleted from the active database but may remain in our archives. 

Exclusions:   
This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data collected by App Discovery Engine other than Personal Data collected through the Services. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to App Discovery Engine through the Services or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Services, such as virtual walls within social networking services, news feeds, forums, any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and App Discovery Engine shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, distribute and exploit such Unsolicited Information without limitation or attribution. 

Children:   
App Discovery Engine does not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any Personal Data through the Services. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Data through the Services without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Data to App Discovery Engine through the Services, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases. 

Links to Other Web Sites: 

Security: 

Other Terms and Conditions: 

Changes to App Discovery Engine’s Privacy Policy: 

Your California Privacy Rights:   
Applicable California privacy legislation permits visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request to access such information, please contact us as follows: support@appdiscoveryengine.com. Within thirty (30) days of receiving such a request, we will provide a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the address specified in this paragraph.   
Access to Information; Contacting App Discovery Engine:   
This Privacy Policy applies only to the Services. The Services may contain links to other web sites not operated or controlled by App Discovery Engine (the “Third Party Sites”). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from the Services do not imply that App Discovery Engine endorses or has reviewed the Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies. 

Integrating Third Party Services:   
One of the special features of the Service is that it allows you to enable or log in to the Service via various online third party services, such as social media and social networking services like Facebook (“Third Party Services”), to be directly integrated into your App Discovery Engine experience. By directly integrating these services, we make your online experiences richer, and more personalized. To take advantage of this feature, we will ask you to log in to the relevant Third Party Services. When you add a Third Party Service account to the Service or log into the Service using your Third Party Services account, we will collect relevant information necessary to enable the Service to access that Third Party Service and your data contained within that Third Party Service. However, please remember that the manner in which Third Party Services use, store and disclose your information is governed solely by the policies of such third parties, and App Discovery Engine shall have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any Third Party Service that may be enabled within the Service. 

App Discovery Engine takes reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data provided via the Services from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet, email or other electronic transmission is ever fully secure or error free, so you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us in this way. 

Your access to and use of the Services is subject to the Terms of Service. 

The Services and our business may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for App Discovery Engine to make changes to this Privacy Policy. App Discovery Engine reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Data. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the Services after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy. 

To keep your Personal Data accurate, current, and complete, please contact us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct Personal Data in our possession that you have previously submitted via the Services. Please also feel free to contact us if you have any questions about App Discovery Engine’s Privacy Policy or the information practices of App Discovery Engine. 

You may contact us as follows:   
App Discovery Engine, Inc. c/o PO BOx 1314, Millbrae, CA 94030
